CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

UX/UI Designer

CONTACT

✓ Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

A Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

SKILLS

Sketching

Design Psychology Front End -

Figma Web Development

Wireframes HTML

Prototyping CSS

User Research JavaScript (JS)

Data Synthesis Git

Usability Testing Bootstrap

Journey Mapping Material UI

UI Design React.js

Adobe Creative Angular.js

Apple iOS

Node.js

EDUCATION

Human Computer
Interaction for UX (Cert.)

MIT

UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

PROFILE

Hi, a bit about me I'm a passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill user needs. A capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. A UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain points, and behaviors.

EXPERIENCE

Application Development Analyst

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- Designed software applications for various operating systems according to business & client requirements
- Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
 - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
 - · Decreased time spent on bugs/defects
- Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

Brand Strategist

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies.
- · Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
 - Designed presentation/contract sign room using visual, auditory, olfactory stimuli
 - · lead to 50% contract signing increase.

All-Source Intelligence Technician

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- Designed first ever non-kinetic targeting product in a cross-functional environment.
- Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- Supervision
 - Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
 - Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
 - Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research.